Finding Aid for University of Michigan Photographs Vertical File ca. 1817-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- History and Description
  - Campus Buildings
    - Medical Building (built 1850)
      - Views from east, northeast, and southeast (Folder D13-236)
      - Views from north (Folder D13-237)
      - Views from south (Folder D13-238)
      - Views from west and northwest (Folder D13-239)
      - Building] Fire and razing (Folder D13-240)
    - [Medical Building (built 1903) see Samuel Trask Dana Natural Resources Building]
    - [Medical Building (built 1925) see Clarence C. Little Science Building]
    - Medical Science Building (Folder D13-241)
    - Michigan League and Lydia Mendelssohn Theatre
      - Interior and exterior views (Folder D13-242)
      - Murals in Ethel Fountain Hussey Room (Folder D13-243)
    - Michigan Stadium (Folder D13-244)
    - Michigan Union (Thomas M. Cooley House) (Folder D13-245)
    - Michigan Union (built 1919)
      - Exterior views (Folder D13-246)
      - Interior views (Folder D13-247)
    - Mimes Theater Building (Folder D13-248)
    - Modern Language Building (Folder D13-249)
    - Morris Hall (Folder D13-250)
    - Mortimer E. Cooley Building (Folder D13-251)
    - Mosher-Jordan Hall (Folder D13-252)
    - [Museum Building (built 1880) see Romance Languages Building]
    - [Museum of Art see Alumni Memorial Hall]
    - Museums Annex (Folder D13-253)
    - [Museums Building (built 1928) see Alexander G. Ruthven Museums Building]
    - [Natural Resources Building see Samuel Trask Dana Natural Resources Building]
    - [Natural Science Building see Edward Henry Kraus Natural Science Building]
    - [Newberry Hall see Kelsey Museum of Archaeology]
    - [Newberry Residence see Helen Newberry Residence]
    - North Hall (Folder D13-254)
    - [Nurses Home (Homeopathic) see Internes Home]
    - [Nurses Residence (built 1921) see Pemberton-Welch Nurses Residence]
    - [Nurses Residence (built 1925) see Couzens Hall]
    - Observatory
      (see folder 86 for photos of telescope)
      - 1854-1868 (Original building) (Folder D13-255)
      - 1868-1908 (With west wing added), 2 folders (Folder D13-256-257)
      - 1908-1954 (With east wing added) (Folder D13-258)
      - 1954-Present (With west wing removed) (Folder D13-259)
    - [Old Engineering Building see Engineering Building (built 1840)]
    - [Old Medical Building see Medical Building (built 1850)]
    - Outpatient Clinic (Folder D13-260)
    - Palmer Field (Folder D13-261)
    - [Palmer Ward see Radiation Laboratory]
    - Pemberton-Welch Nurses Residence (Folder D13-262)
    - [Pharmacology Building see Economics Building]
    - Phoenix Building (Folder D13-M)
      medium size only
    - [Physics-Astronomy Building see David M. Dennison Physics and Astronomy Building]
    - [Physics Building see Harrison M. Randall Laboratory and West Physics Building]
    - Portage Lake Observatory (Folder D13-263)
    - Power Center for the Performing Arts (Folder D13-264)
    - President's House, 2 folders (Folder D13-265-266)
    - [Professors' House, North University Avenue, East (built 1840) see Dental Building (1891-1908)]
    - [Professors' House, North University Avenue, West (built 1840) see Psychological Laboratory]
    - [Professors' House, South University Avenue, East (built 1840) see Engineering Building]
    - [Professors' House, South University Avenue, West (built 1840) see President's House]
    - Psychological Laboratory (built 1840, North University Avenue) (Folder D13-267)
    - [Psychopathic Hospital (built 1906) see Beal Residence]
    - [Public Health Building see Henry F. Vaughan Public Health Building and Thomas Francis Jr. School of Public Health Building]
    - R.O.T.C. Building (Old Heating Plant) (Folder D13-268)
    - Rackham Building
      - Construction (Folder D13-269)
      - Exterior views (Folder D13-270)
      - Interior views (Folder D13-271)
    - Radiation Laboratory (Folder D13-272)
    - [Randall Laboratory see Harrison M. Randall Laboratory]
    - [Regents Plaza see Fleming Administration Building]
    - Research Administration Building (Folder D13-273)
    - [Residential College see East Quadrangle]
    - Romance Languages Building
      - Views from east (Folder D13-274)
      - Views from west (Folder D13-275-276)
      - Details, interiors and demolition (Folder D13-277)
    - [Ruthven Museums Building see Alexander G. Ruthven Museums Building]
    - Samuel Trask Dana Natural Resources Building (Folder D13-278)
    - School of Dentistry Building (built 1971) (Folder D13-279)
    - School of Education Building (Folder D13-280)
    - School of Music Building (Maynard Street) (Folder D13-281)
    - School of Music Building (North Campus) (Folder D13-282)
    - [School of Natural Resources Building see Samuel Trask Dana Natural Resources Building]
    - [School of Public Health Building see Henry F. Vaughan Public Health Building and Thomas Francis Jr. School of Public Health Building]
    - Simpson Memorial Institute (Folder D13-283)
    - South College (Folder D13-284)
    - South Quadrangle (Folder D13-285)
    - Space Research Building (Folder D13-286)
    - [Stadium see Michigan Stadium]
    - Statuary, monuments, etc.
      - Class boulders and trees (including Tappan Oak) (Folder D13-287)
      - Professor's Monument and Franklin Statue (Folder D13-288)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder D13-289)
    - Stockwell Hall (Folder D13-290)
    - Student Publications Building (Folder D13-291)
    - Students' Observatory (Folder D13-292)
    - Surveying Building (Folder D13-293)
    - Tappan Hall (Folder D13-294)
    - Thomas Francis Jr. School of Public Health Building (Folder D13-295)
    - [Thomas Henry Simpson Memorial Institute see Simpson Memorial Institute]
    - Undergraduate Library (Folder D13-296)
    - University Hall
      - Old dome (1872-1896)
        - Construction and views from east (Folder D13-297)
        - Views from west before remodeling of 1879 (Folder D13-298)
        - Views from west, 1879-1896; 2 folders (Folder D13-299-300)
      - No dome (1897-1898) (Folder D13-301)
      - New dome (1898-1950)
        - Views from east (Folder D13-302)
        - Views from west, 1898-1924 (Folder D13-303)
        - Views from west, (with Angell Hall), also interiors, 1924-1950 (Folder D13-304)
      - Opening the cornerstone, 1950 (Folder D13-305)
      - Interiors: Auditorium and Frieze Memorial Organ (Folder D13-306)
    - [University High School see School of Education Building]
    - [University Hospital (1875-1891) see Dental Building (1891-1908)]
    - [University Hospital (built 1891, Catherine Street) see Institute for Social Research Building (Catherine Street)]
    - University Hospital (built 1925) (Folder D13-307)
    - [University Museum Building (built 1880) see Romance Languages Building]
    - [University Museums Building (built 1928) see Alexander G. Ruthven Museums Building]
    - University Terrace Apartments (Folder D13-308)
    - [Vaughan Building see Henry F. Vaughan Public Health Building]
    - Vera Baits Houses (Folder D13-309)
    - Veterans Village (Hill Street) (Folder D13-310)
    - Victor C. Vaughan House (Folder D13-311)
    - W. K. Kellogg Foundation Institute (Folder D13-312)
    - Waterman Gymnasium [see also Barbour Gymnasium]
      - 1894-1902 (before Barbour was built) (Folder D13-313)
      - 1902-1916 (with Barbour) (Folder D13-314)
      - 1916-1977 (after expansion; includes demolition, 1977) (Folder D13-315)
      - Construction and interiors (Folder D13-316)
    - West Engineering Annex
      - 1885-1888 (original building) (Folder D13-317)
      - 1888-1900 (addition with tower)
        - Views from northeast (Folder D13-318)
        - Views from northwest (Folder D13-319)
      - 1900-1918 (with wings extended south) (Folder D13-320)
      - 1918-1956 (with clock added to tower) (Folder D13-321)
    - West Engineering Building (Folder D13-322)
    - West Hall (Folder D13-323)
    - [West Medical Building see Samuel Trask Dana Natural Resources Building]
    - West Physics Building
      - 1888-1905 (original building) (Folder D13-324)
      - 1905-1966 (with addition; includes fire, 1966) (Folder D13-325)
    - West Quadrangle (Folder D13-326)
    - William L. Clements Library (Folder D13-327)
    - Willow Village (Folder D13-328)
    - Women's Athletic Building (built 1912, State Street) (Folder D13-329)
    - Women's Athletic Building (built 1928, Forest (now Washtenaw) Avenue) (Folder D13-330)
    - [Women's League see Michigan League]
    - Yost Ice Arena (Yost Field House) (Folder D13-331)
- Special Celebrations and Events
  The Special Celebrations and Events series documents a variety of campus ceremonies, customs and events including formal university events such as commencements and inaugurations of presidents, as well as student social events such as the freshman-sophomore rush, J-Hop, Lantern Night and the Spring Games. The series also includes photos depicting the university's involvement the Civil War, World War I and World War II.
  - Commencement
    - (undated) Commencement (Folder E3-332)
    - 1905 Commencement (Folder E3-M)
    - 1907 Commencement (Folder E3-332)
    - 1912 Commencement (Folder E3-334)
    - 1914 Commencement (Folder E3-335)
    - 1915 Commencement (Folder E3-336)
    - 1919 Commencement (Folder E3-337)
    - 1923 Commencement (Folder E3-338)
    - 1924 Commencement (Folder E3-339)
    - 1926 Commencement (Folder E3-340)
    - 1927 Commencement (Folder E3-34)
    - 1945 Commencement (Folder E3-342)
    - 1960 Commencement (Folder E3-343)
    - 1964 Commencement (Folder E3-344)
  - Inaugurals
    - Marion Leroy Burton Inaugurals (Folder E13-345)
  - Anniversaries
    - U of M 75th Anniversary, 1912 (Folder E17-346)
    - U of M Centennial, 1937-Exhibit photos (Folder E17-347)
  - Special Events
    - Cap Night (Folder E25-348)
    - Convocations: Honors (Folder E25-349)
    - Freshman Sophomore Rush (Folder E25-350)
    - Junior Hop (Folder E25-351)
    - Lantern Night (Folder E25-352)
    - Laws versus Lits (Folder E25-353)
    - Salk Vaccine, Announcement of (Folder E25-354)
    - Senior Swing Out, 1903, 1909, 1913, 1915 (Folder E25-355)
    - Spring Games (Folder E25-356)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder E25-357)
      (includes dedication of Angell portrait)
  - Emergencies and Wars
    - U of M & the Civil War (Folder E27-358)
    - U of M & World War I (Folder E27-359)
    - U of M & World War II
      - Army Units
        - Miscellaneous (Folder E27b-360)
        - Army Specialized Training Program (Folder E27b-361)
        - Company A, 365 1st Service Unit (Army Japanese Language School) (Folder E27b-362)
        - Co. B-4 (Meteorology School) (Folder E27b-363)
        - Specialized Training Program (Folder E27b-364)
        - R.O.T.C. (Folder E27b-365)
        - W.A.C. (Folder E27b-366)
      - Navy and Marine Corps Units, 2 folders (Folder E27b-367/8)
      - United Service Organization (USO) (Folder E27b-369)
      - Wartime Student Activities Women (Folder E27l-370)
      - Manpower Mobilization Corps (Folder E27l-371)
    - Veterans (Folder E27m-372)
    - U of M & Viet Nam (Folder E27-373)
- Student Life and Customs
  The Student Life and Customs series documents many aspects of student life from living conditions (19th century boarding rooms to modern dormitories) to social organizations, literary and musical societies, honorary societies, fraternities and sororities and intercollegiate and recreational sports. The series is organized largely around specific student organizations or activities. A General subseries, organized chronologically, includes images not tied to specific organizations or events. The organizational photos often include group photos, shots of an office or house, and special activities.
  - General
    - Undated (Folder F1-374)
    - 1900-1930 (Folder F1-375)
    - 1930-1970 (Folder F1-376)
  - Student Publications
    - Miscellaneous (Folder F3 377)
    - The Michigan Daily (Folder F3g-378)
  - Men's Organizations
    - Michigan Union (Folder F15)
  - Women's Organizations
    - Michigan League and Michigan Dames (Folder F17-379)
    - Philologia (Folder F17-380)
  - Musical Organizations
    - Men's Glee Club (includes Glee, Banjo and Mandolin Clubs) (Folder F19-381)
    - University orchestra (Folder F19-382)
    - Women and girl's glee clubs and Amphion Club (Folder F19-383)
  - Literary Organizations
    - Adelphi and Alpha Nu Literary Societies), 2 folders (Folder F21-384-385)
  - Departmental Clubs
    - Engineering Society (Folder F22-387)
  - National Origins and Foreign Interest Groups
    - Miscellaneous (Folder F23-388)
  - Scientific Groups
    - Stowell Microscopic Club (Folder F25-389)
  - Religious Groups
    - Miscellaneous (Folder F27-390)
  - Social Clubs
    - O'Toole Club (Folder F40-391)
    - Smokers' Club (Folder F40-392)
    - Southern Club (Folder F40-393)
  - Honorary Societies and Professional Fraternities
    - Barristers (Folder F41-M)
    - Druids, 2 folders (Folder F41-394-395)
      (cataloged separately)
    - Gamma Eta Gama (Law Fraternity)
    - Michigamua (Folder F41-396)
    - Morter Board (Folder F41-397)
    - Nu Sigma Nu (Medical) (Folder F41-398)
    - Phi Alpha Delta (Law) (Folder F41-399)
    - Phi Beta Pi (Folder F41-400)
    - Phi Delta Phi: Kent Chapter (Folder F41-401)
    - Phi Mu Alpha (Music) (Folder F41-402)
    - Phi Rho Sigma (Folder F41-403)
    - Sigma Gamma Epsilon (Folder F4-404)
    - Sinfonic (Folder F41-M)
    - Triangles (Folder F41-405)
    - Xi Psi Phi (Dental) (Folder F41-M)
  - Housing
    - Off-campus: Student Rooming Houses (Exteriors) (Folder F43-406)
    - Off-campus: Student Rooms (Interiors), 4 folders (Folder F43-407-410)
    - University Dormitories (Folder F44-411)
    - University Housing: Martha Cook (Folder F44-412)
    - Northwood Apartments (Folder F44-413)
  - Social Fraternities and Sororities
    - Acacia (Folder F47-414)
    - Alpha Chi Omega (Folder F47-415)
    - Alpha Delta Phi, 3 folders (Folder F47-416-418)
    - Alpha Kappa Lambda (Folder F47 418a)
    - Alpha Omicron Pi (Folder F47-419)
    - Alpha Phi (Folder F47-420)
    - Alpha Sigma Phi (Folder F47-421)
    - Alpha Tau Omega (Folder F47-422)
    - Beta Theta Pi (Folder F47-423)
    - Chi Psi [see also Counseling Center in UBImus (Folder F47-424)
      also medium D13 for earlier chapter house
    - Collegiate Sorosis
    - Delta Chi (Folder F47-426)
    - Delta Gamma (Folder F47-427)
    - Delta Kappa Epsilon, 2 folders (Folder F47-428-429)
    - Delta Phi (Folder F47-430)
    - Delta Theta Phi (Folder F47-431)
    - Delta Upsilon (Folder F47-432)
    - Gamma Phi Beta (Folder F47-433)
    - Hermitage Order (Folder F47-433a)
      (includes 1938-1939 Directory)
    - Kappa Alpha Theta (Folder F47-434)
    - Kappa Kappa Gamma (Folder F47-435)
    - Kappa Sigma (Folder F47-436)
    - Phi Alpha Gamma (Folder F47-437)
    - Phi Beta Pi (Folder F47-438)
    - Phi Delta Theta (Folder F47-439)
    - Phi Gamma Delta (Folder F47-440)
    - Phi Kappa Psi (Folder F47-441)
    - Phi Kappa Sigma (Folder F47-M)
    - Phi Kappa Tau-L (Folder F47-M)
    - Phi Sigma Kappa (Folder F47-L)
    - Pi Beta Phi (Folder F47-442)
    - Pi Lambda Phi (Folder F47-442)
    - Psi Upsilon (Folder F47-443)
    - Sigma Alpha Epsilon (Folder F47-444)
    - Sigma Chi (Folder F47-445)
    - Sigma Nu (Folder F47-446)
    - Sigma Phi (Folder F47-447)
    - Sigma Sigma (Folder F47-448)
    - Sigma Upsilon (Folder F47-449)
    - Theta Delta Chi (Folder F47-450)
    - Trigon (Folder F47-451)
    - Zeta Psi (Folder F47-452)
    - Zeta Tau Alpha (Folder F47-453)
  - Cooperatives
    - Michigan Wolverine Student Cooperative (Folder F54-M)
  - Eating Clubs
    - Eating Houses (Folder F55-454)
  - University Dramatics & Theater Activities
    - Miscellaneous (Folder F65-455)
    - Broadcasting (Folder F69-456)
    - Comedy Club (Folder F71-457)
    - Julius Caesar Group (Folder F71-M)
    - Junior Girls Play (Folder F71-458)
    - Michigan Union Opera (Mimes) (Folder F71-459)
    - Play Production (Folder F71-460)
    - Dance Organizations and Groups
      - Modern Dance Club (Folder F72-461)
  - Student Celebrations and Carnivals
    - Miscellaneous (Folder F75-462)
  - Intercollegiate Sports
    - Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Folder F81-ML)
    - Baseball (Folder F84-463)
    - Basketball (Folder F84-464)
    - Basketball, Women's (Folder F84-465)
    - Crew (Folder F84-M)
    - Football
      - Fans, 1900-1919 (Folder F84-466)
      - First football team, 1879 (Folder F84-467)
      - Game photos (Folder F84-468)
      - Teams and players, 1890-1899 (Folder F84-469)
      - Teams and players, 1900-1919; 2 folders (Folder F84-470-471)
      - Teams and players, 1920-1939 (Folder F84-472)
      - Teams and players, 1940-1959 (Folder F84-473)
      - Teams and players, 1960-1969 (Folder F84-474)
    - Golf (Folder F84-475)
    - Hockey (Folder F84-476)
    - Swimming (Folder F84-477)
    - Track (Folder F84-478)
  - Intra-mural and Recreational Sports (Folder F86-479)
  - University Bands (Folder F90-480)
- Class Photos, 1858-1956
  The Class Photos series includes group and composite photographs of graduating classes from various schools colleges and departments as well as some photos of class reunions and photographs of individual students arranged by graduating class. Some of the class year and school identifications are very uncertain.
  - Classes by Year: Group portraits and reunions
    - Classes, unidentified (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1858 (Folder F99-L)
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-481)
    - Class of 1859
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-482)
    - Class of 1861
      - Medical (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1862
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-M)
      - Medical (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1863
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-483)
    - Class of 1864
      - Medical (Folder F99-484)
    - Class of 1865
      - Law (Folder F99-485)
    - Class of 1866
      - Medical (Folder F99-486)
    - Class of 1867
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-487)
    - Class of 1868
      - Engineering (Folder F99-488)
      - Medical (Folder F99-488)
    - Class of 1869
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-489)
    - Classes of 1870s (unidentified) (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1870
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1871
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-490)
    - Class of 1872
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-491)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-491)
    - Class of 1873
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-492)
      - Law (Folder F99-492)
      - Medical (Folder F99-492)
    - Class of 1874
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-493)
      - Medical (Folder F99-493)
    - Class of 1875
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-494)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-494)
      - Medical (Folder F99-494)
    - Class of 1876
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-495)
      - Medical (Folder F99-495)
      - Law (Folder F99-495)
    - Class of 1877
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-496)
      - Law (Folder F99-496)
        also tintype (in UBImux F99), medium and large
    - Class of 1878
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-497)
      - Law (Folder F99-497)
      - Architecture (Folder F99-497)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-497)
      - Pharmacy (Folder F99-497)
    - Class of 1879
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-498)
    - Classes of 1880s (unidentified) (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1880
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-499)
      - Law (Folder F99-499)
    - Class of 1881
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-500)
      - Law (Folder F99-500)
    - Class of 1882
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-501)
      - Law (Folder F99-501)
      - Dental (Folder F99-501)
    - Class of 1883
      - Pharmacy (Folder F99-502)
    - Class of 1884
      - Homeopathy (Folder F99-502.5)
    - Class of 1885
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1886
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-503)
      - Law (Folder F99-503)
      - Medical (Folder F99-503)
      - Pharmacy (Folder F99-503)
    - Class of 1887
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-504)
      - Dental (Folder F99-504)
      - Medical (Folder F99-504)
    - Class of 1888
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-505)
      - Law (Folder F99-505)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-505)
    - Class of 1889
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-506)
      - Dental (Folder F99-506)
    - Classes of 1890s (unidentified) (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1890
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-507)
      - Dental (Folder F99-507)
    - Class of 1891
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-ML)
      - Law (Folder F99-ML)
    - Class of 1892
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-508)
      - Pharmacy (Folder F99-508)
    - Class of 1893
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-509)
      - Law (Folder F99-509)
      - Pharmacy (Folder F99-509)
    - Class of 1894
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-ML)
      - Law (Folder F99-ML)
    - Class of 1895
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-510)
      - Law (Folder F99-510)
    - Class of 1896
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-511)
      - Law (Folder F99-511)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-511)
      - Dental (Folder F99-511)
    - Class of 1897
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-512)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-512)
    - Class of 1898
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-513)
      - Law (Folder F99-513)
    - Class of 1899
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-514)
      - Law (Folder F99-514)
      - Medical (Folder F99-514)
    - Class of 1900
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-515)
      - Law (Folder F99-515)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-515)
    - Class of 1901
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-516)
      - Law (Folder F99-516)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-516)
      - Medical (Folder F99-516)
      - Pharmacy (Folder F99-516)
    - Class of 1902
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-517)
      - Law (Folder F99-517)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-517)
      - Dental (Folder F99-517)
    - Class of 1903
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-518)
      - Law (Folder F99-518)
    - Class of 1904
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-519)
      - Law (Folder F99-519)
      - Medical (Folder F99-519)
    - Class of 1905
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-L)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1906
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1907
      - Law (Folder F99)
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-520)
      - Medical
    - Class of 1908
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1909
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-L)
      - Dental (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1910
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1912
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-M)
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-ML)
      - Library Science (Folder F99-M)
        medium
    - Class of 1913
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-521)
      - Law (Folder F99-521)
      - Library Science (Folder F99-521)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-521)
    - Class of 1914
      - Engineering (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1915
      - Literature & Art (Folder F99-522)
      - Law (Folder F99-522)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-522)
    - Class of 1916
      - Law (Folder F99-523)
      - Engineering (Folder F99-523)
      - Medical (Folder F99-523)
    - Class of 1917
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-ML)
      - Dental (Folder F99-ML)
    - Class of 1918
      - Library Science (Folder F99-524)
      - Medical (Folder F99-524)
      - Nursing (Folder F99-524)
      - Homeopathic Training School
    - Class of 1919
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-525)
      - Medical (Folder F99-525)
    - Class of 1920
      - Medical (Folder F99-526)
    - Class of 1921
      - Literature & Arts (Folder F99-527)